Jacob Adamson

376 S Lincoln St Denver, CO 80209

303.921.8358 Jakeladamson0@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Over 15 years of experience as an ambitious, hardworking, professional with storied background in clerical and customer service experience with an emphasis of highly analytical and organizational skills, strong interpersonal communication skills, problem analysis and solving, all while consistently receiving positive customer and co-worker feedback.

SKILLS

- Extensive technical/computer background
- Internal and external customer support
- Interpersonal communications
- Works well with others as well as independently as needed

EXPERIENCE

Full Time Student/Full Stack Developer- University of Denver

Denver, CO - 2017-2021

I am currently in a full time coding program through University of Denver, studying to be a certified Full Stack Developer. I am learning Javascript, HTML, CSS, and many more skills.

Payroll Processor/Parts Procurement I, Hussmann Services

Denver, CO - 2017-2021

Review time sheets, work charts, wage computation, and other information to detect and reconcile payroll discrepancies. Compile employee time, production, and payroll data from time sheets and other records. Prepare purchase orders and review requisitions for goods and services. Take ownership of extra clerical tasks such as operating accounting software to analyze invoices to ensure timely payment to vendors within net terms.

Dispatcher I/Parts Procurement I, Hussmann Services

Denver, CO - 2015-2017

Schedule or dispatch workers and equipment to appropriate locations based on customer requests, specifications, or needs, using job boards, computers, and telephones. Prepare purchase orders and review requisitions for goods and services. Take ownership of extra clerical tasks such as operating accounting software to analyze invoices to ensure timely payment to vendors within net terms. Review time sheets, work charts, wage computation, and other information to detect and reconcile payroll discrepancies. Compile employee time, production, and payroll data from time sheets and other records.

Accomplishments

- Met and exceeded all GDP and personal growth goals during every year of employment.
- Developed and generated a weekly work order aging report for Team Leads and Service Management to use to satisfy customer work orders in a timely and efficient fashion.

Inside Sales, Sid Harvey's Industries

Denver, CO - 2011-2015

Wholesale HVAC and refrigeration sales, customer service/support in store, via telephone, and email. Prepared purchase orders, solicited bid proposals, and reviewed requisitions for goods and services.

Accomplishments

• Doubled annual sales of several accounts.

Inside Sales/Warehouse Clerk, Dennis Supply Co.

Casper, WY - 2007-2011

Handled customers in store, via telephone, and provided email support for a wholesale company in HVAC and refrigeration. Also managed every facet of transactions from point of sale to picking and shipping/delivering orders as needed. Prepared purchase orders, solicited bid proposals, and reviewed requisitions for goods and services.

Accomplishments

- Increased sales by going above and beyond for every customer.
- Obtained extensive warehouse management experience.

Customer Service Agent, OfficeMax Call Center

Casper, WY - 2004-2006

Accomplishments

- Proficient in immediate general call queue support.
- Became a specialized customer care team member.

Master Control Operator, KTWO Television

Casper, WY - 2002-2004

Monitored strength, clarity, and reliability of incoming and outgoing signals and adjusted equipment as necessary to maintain quality broadcasts. Observed monitors and conversed with station personnel to determine audio and video levels and to ascertain that programs were airing. Monitored and logged transmitter readings. Reported equipment problems, ensured that repairs were made, and made emergency repairs to equipment when necessary and possible.

Accomplishments

- Earned a position from Production Assistant to Master Control Operator within a year of employment.
- Earned a position as lead Master Control Operator within two years of employment.

EDUCATION

University of Denver

202

Studying Full Stack Development

Art Of Audio

2015

Studied Audio Engineering

Casper College

2001-2002

Studied Sound Reinforcement

References available upon request.